RG 062:058, Town of Griswold
Connecticut State Library
Town of Griswold records
1829-1980
Connecticut State Library
Griswold (Conn.)
32 cubic feet
Administrative, election, and school records for the town of Griswold.
RG062_058
Multiple
Historical Note
The town of Griswold was incorporated in October 1815 and was taken from Preston.
Scope and Content
Administrative, election, and school records for the town of Griswold.
Index Terms
Subjects:
School enrollment -- Connecticut -- Griswold; Deeds -- Connecticut -- Griswold; Tax assessment -- Connecticut -- Griswold -- Registers; Taxation -- Connecticut -- Griswold -- Registers; Local taxation -- Connecticut -- Griswold -- Registers; Property tax -- Connecticut -- Griswold -- Registers
Places:
Griswold (Conn.) -- Records and correspondence
Restrictions on Access
These records are stored at an off-site facility and therefore may not be available on a same-day basis.
See the policy.
Container List
- Records, 1829-1980
  - T000328
    - Petitions against liquor licenses, 1829-1830 (Box Box 1)
    - Dog license, 1897 (Box Box 1)
    - List of voters, circa 1903 (Box Box 1)
    - Liquor license applications, 1910-1911 (Box Box 1)
    - Town orders, bills and receipts, 1907-1909 (Box Box 1)
    - School records including minutes of meetings, accounts, enumerations, deeds, insurance policies, blue prints of 12th School District, 1842-1901 (Box Box 2)
  - 2008-004
    - Tax Abstracts
      There are two tax abstracts, one for the Borough of Jewett City and one for the Town of Griswold, for the year 1895, and thereafter from 1900 through 1980.
      Boxes 3 and 12 are located on oversize shelving.
      - 1864, 1865, 1868, 1870, 1871, 1872, 1873, 1874, 1875, 1876, 1877, 1878, 1879 (Box Box 3)
      - 1880, 1881, 1882, 1883, 1884, 1885 (Box Box 4)
      - 1886, 1887, 1888, 1889, 1890, 1891 (Box Box 5)
      - 1892, 1893, 1894, 1895 (Box Box 6)
      - 1896, 1897, 1898, 1899, 1900 (Box Box 7)
      - 1901, 1902, 1903 (Box Box 8)
      - 1904, 1905, 1906 (Box Box 9)
      - 1907, 1908, 1909 (Box Box 10)
      - 1910, 1911, 1912 (Box Box 11)
      - 1913, 1914, 1915 (Box Box 12)
      - 1916, 1917, 1918, 1919, 1920, 1921, 1922, 1923, 1924, 1925, 1926, 1927, 1928, 1929, 1930, 1931, 1932, 1933, 1934, 1935, 1936, 1937, 1938, 1939, 1940, 1941, 1942, 1943, 1944, 1945, 1946, 1947, 1948, 1949, 1950, 1951, 1952, 1953, 1954, 1955, 1956, 1957, 1958, 1959, 1960, 1961, 1962, 1963, 1964, 1965, 1966, 1967, 1968, 1969, 1970, 1971, 1972, 1973, 1974, 1975, 1976, 1977, 1978, 1979, 1980, 129 volumes
      - undated, 1 volume
    - Personnel property tax, 1954; 1 volume
    - Real estate, undated; 1 volume